Liam Moreland - Customer Service and Management

Central Coast, Australia, 0421460290, morelandliam@gmail.com

-	~1	
Pre	าโป	Δ

Dedicated and passionate professional with over 6 years of experience in retail, and 2 years collective experience in leadership. I have a proven track record of enhancing customer experiences through genuine engagement and exceptional service, by going above and beyond the expectation.

Employment History

Aug 2024 - Present

UX Designer Internship, NIB Thrive

• Contributed to the redesign of the platform's navigation to improve staff workflows. We identified UI redundancies and integrated existing user workarounds into the platform, resulting in a more efficient UX.

Nov 2023 - Feb 2024

Product Management Internship - Optus

- Initiated an end-to-end design solution to prevent password sharing. By
 using agile methodology and collaboration with designers and development,
 our solution prevented 14,000 accounts from password sharing.
- Designed the UI mock-ups using Figma, for Optus Sport password sharing journey and TV app video player.

Jul 2023 - Nov 2023

Team leader - Canon Store

- Led a large team of 25, working on business process outsourcing.
- Oversaw the development of training plans for new employees. By collaboratively with leadership to implement instructional design practices, we successfully halved the initial onboarding time.

Aug 2022 - Jul 2023

Assistant Manager - Oscar Wylee

- Led a small team of 6, while working closely with management to achieve business KPI's and improve customer experience.
- Introduced customer-centric sales strategies specific to our stores demographic, that drove positive online reviews over the period of 6 months.

Jul 2017 - Aug 2022

Customer Assistant - Oscar Wylee

- Retail sales, focusing on lasting customer relationships.
- Successfully hit store-set KPI's consistently over a 5 year period, this improved my time taken to make sales and quality of customer experience.

Education

Feb 2020 - Nov 2023

Bachelor of Design (Interaction Design) - University of Canberra

- Vice President of the Design Society
- · Graduated with a high distinction GPA

Skills & Technologies

- Effective communication
- Microsoft suite
- Empathy and emotional intelligence
- Adobe suite
- Problem-Solving Skills
- · POS systems